wittyfeed.me 2019-10-29

# Privacy Policy

Thank you for visiting our Privacy Policy page. Here, we are to mention what information do we collect. We call this information "Personally Identifiable Information" (also commonly referred to as personal data). This can be understood as all data that can be used to identify you. The following types of data about you may be collected on your visits to our website: 

  * your IP address;
  * your operating system and browser software used to access our website;
  * story related information which you read;
  * your demographics (Country, City, Language etc);
  * your unique numeric identification;
  * your device information and cookies;
  * in the event you contact us by email, we may keep a record of that correspondence; such record may include, apart from your email address the Personally Identifiable Information that you will include in the communication.

Use of Personal Data by us. We collect and use your Personally Identifiable Information for the following legitimate business purposes:

  * for general data analysis and to run our website better;
  * for generating statistics and measuring web traffic and to understand the popularity of specific areas of our website;
  * for identifying usage trends and expanding our business activities;
  * for building higher quality and providing a better user experience by tracking the behavior of our users;
  * for complying with applicable legal requirements and satisfying requests by governmental and supervisory authorities;
  * for identifying and preventing fraud.

Except as set forth in this Policy or as specifically agreed to by you, we will not disclose any of your Personally Identifiable Information. We may disclose and otherwise use Personally Identifiable Information as described below.

Affiliates.

We share your Personally Identifiable Information with our affiliates — companies that control, are controlled by, or are under common control with Vatsana Technologies Pvt Ltd.

Our Partners.

We allow third party advertising companies including carefully selected ad networks and business partners (referred to as "Our Partners"), to serve ads when you visit our website. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, [Click here](https://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp).

Service Providers. 

Your information may be collected by entities that provide services to us, including companies that deliver web analytics, data processing, data enhancement and customer insights, advertising, email distribution, and other services.

Other Parties (when required by law or as necessary to protect our services). We may disclose your information (including Personally Identifiable Information) to other parties in order to: 

  * protect our legal rights or property, the legal rights or property of our affiliates, and sites or services we offer;
  * protect the rights, safety, and security of our users, ourselves, or any other person or entity;
  * prevent fraud (or for risk management purposes);
  * in order to comply with or respond to the law or legal process or a request for cooperation by a governmental or supervisory authority, whether or not legally required.

Usually, we maintain centralized servers and systems in Europe and may maintain servers and systems elsewhere. These servers and systems are managed by us or on our behalf, or by our affiliates. 

In the event of transfer and processing of your Personally Identifiable Information outside the EEA, we will make sure that the information receives the same level of protection as if it remained within the EEA using the EU Commission approved Standard Contractual Clauses, or by relying on certification schemes such as the EU-US Privacy Shield.

We use commercially reasonable physical, electronic, and procedural safeguards to protect your Personally Identifiable Information from misuse and unauthorized access, disclosure, alteration, and destruction in accordance with the requirements of applicable laws. 

Considering you are an individual browsing from the EU/EEA, where the General Data Protection Regulations apply, you can exercise rights related to your data by contacting us via contact details at the bottom of the page. 

The information collected by Our Partners is used to analyze trends, understand user activities and gather demographic information to enable, manage and develop their personalized ads and related services. This type of information does not identify you personally and, typically, is aggregated with other data to create segments – groups of users and general interest categories that are inferred based on a range of factors. 

Our content is aimed at a general audience. We do not knowingly target, collect, use or share information that could reasonably be used to identify children under the age of 15 without prior parental consent or consistent with applicable law. By using our service you confirm that you either are of legal age or have an applicable consent. 

Our website may display links to websites of third party content providers, other than Our Partners. We do not disclose your Personally Identifiable Information to third parties without obtaining your consent specifically permitting such disclosure. We do not endorse and are not responsible for the privacy practices and content of such third parties. We encourage you to review their privacy policies to understand how they collect and process your Personally Identifiable Information.

We may amend or update this Privacy Policy from time to time. So, one should check it periodically where changes are made, we will post the revised Policy here with an updated effective date.
